# Jayven Couch

+1 (214)-883-4080

jayvencouch.com

linkedin.com/in/jayvencouch

in

github.com/JayvenC

jayvencouch11@gmail.com

I am a true professional who consistently achieves goals and beats deadlines, without cutting corners and losing sight of core values. Aside from experience and education, I am well-equipped with the levels of energy & determination that is required to work under pressure, surpass goals, and multi-task. I am excited for the next opportunity in store for me to proceed in my career.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Science Labs Assistant

Hawaii Pacific University

10/2021 - 12/2021

- Responsibilities
- Perform and/or assist in the preparation of all solutions, chemical, reagents, media, etc. needed to support laboratory sessions.
- Perform data entry of various laboratory supplies and chemicals.

#### Ranch Technician

Majestic Bison Ranch

05/2012 - 05/2021

- Responsibilities
- Effectively handled diets & well-being of a wide variety of animals
- Operated machinery to coordinate land projects that would benefit the environment

## Shop Diver

Negril Adventure Divers

06/2014 - 07/2019

- Responsibilities
- Part-time work conducted in Negril, Jamaica where I managed web services and shop, while accompanying guests on dives

# Billing Manager

Four Corners Logistics LLC

04/2015 - 08/2017

- Responsibilities
- Organized and processed invoices/paperwork for billing department.

#### **EDUCATION**

## O Bachelors of Science in Marine Science Eckerd College

08/2017 - 05/2021 3.5 GPA

Minors

Psychology & Chemistry

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Scripting (Python, JavaScript, Bash & C)

Operating Systems (Linux) Cloud (AWS & GCP)

CI/CD (Jenkins) Containers (Docker)

Container Orchestration (Kubernetes)

IAC (Ansible & Terraform) Version Control (Git)

Monitoring (Prometheus)

Front-End Development (HTML/CSS)

Microsoft Office (Excel, PowerPoint, etc.)

Network Protocols

## **CERTIFICATIONS & COURSES\***

AWS Certified Solutions Architect - Associate

Red Hat® Certified System Administrator (RHCSA)

- \*Complete Linux Training Course 2022 by Imran Afzal via Udemy
- \*CS50x's Introduction to Computer Science

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

Communication	• • • • •
Interpersonal & Collaboration	• • • • •
Problem-Solving	$\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$
Flexible & Adaptable	• • • • •